Ms Geng,
耿小姐
Please set up
我想麻烦您
a meeting between Ji Yuheng
安排代瑞的纪昱恒
from Dairui and Mr. Xia.
跟夏总见一面
Why do you think
你为什么觉得
he could meet Xia Mingrui through me?
可以通过我见到夏明睿
Honestly, I'm not sure.
其实我自己也不确定
I also realize
也知道
that you probably won't help me.
您大概率是不会帮我
But I truly
但是我真的
have no other options left.
没有其他路可以选了
I can only muster the courage
我只能硬着头皮
to give it a try.
试一试
Sorry about this.
麻烦您了
I'm sorry,
对不起
but I can do nothing for this.
这个忙我帮不了你
Sorry, but I have
我先走了
a press conference to attend.
我还有一场发布会要开
If you want more payment
关于上次的事情
for the help
你还想要
you provided me,
更多的感谢费的话
you can reach out to my assistant.
可以联系我的助理
I'll do my best to accommodate.
我都会尽量满足的
Ms. Geng,
耿小姐
I understand.
我知道
Relationships between people
人与人之间的关系
are quite complex.
是很复杂的
Sometimes it even takes
有时候甚至需要
years of effort
长年累月
under immense pressure
顶着巨大的压力
to maintain them.
才能够维持
The hardships involved
这其中的辛苦
are only known to oneself.
也只有自己才知道吧
I truly empathize with you.
我很理解您
If it weren't for
如果不到
a last resort,
迫不得已的地步
I wouldn't come to you.
我真的不会来找您的
Are you threatening me?
你是在威胁我吗
Of course not.
当然不是
I'm here to
我是来求您
ask for your help.
帮我这个忙
I'm not sure
我不知道
how much you know about
你对我和夏明睿的关系
me and Xia Mingrui.
到底了解多少
But I absolutely won't
但是我绝对不会
let our relationship
让我们的关系
become a weapon against us.
变成别人手中的武器
Ms. Geng!
耿小姐
Just so happens
正好
my visa hasn't expired,
签证没过期
and the bank has approved my trip.
行里又肯特批我出去
Plus, I'm familiar with the US.
而且美国那边我也熟
I think if we think of a way,
我觉得想想办法
we can definitely meet Mr. Xia.
总归是能见到夏总的
That's a good idea.
这倒是个办法
He's always busy in China,
夏总在国内没时间
maintaining a tight schedule.
很紧张
Since in the US,
去了美国
he should have some free time.
总能清闲一点吧
Let's hope so.
希望吧
In any case,
总之呢
I'll be available 24/7
我二十四小时
to accommodate his schedule.
配合他的时间
I hope his itinerary
希望他的行程
isn't too packed.
别安排得太满
You really have guts,
还是你有魄力
just going for it.
说走就走
Don't praise me just yet.
先别着急夸
Hold it until I secure the deal.
等谈成了再夸还来得及
I also wonder
也不知道
if it doesn't work out,
如果没谈成的话
will my airfare be reimbursed?
行里给不给我报销机票
But what if
那万一
his schedule is uncertain?
夏总那边时间没个准数
Are you planning to
你就打算
just stay in the US for him?
一直脱岗在美国等他
The higher-ups
上面
would have a problem with it.
会有意见的
Also,
还有
that "you-know-who" from S2
二部那位
might stir up
你走之后
some trouble
指不定在中间
after you leave.
搅什么浑水呢
That's true.
是啊
So I called you over,
所以我喊你过来
hoping that
就是希望
while I'm away,
我不在的这段时间里啊
you can keep an eye
部门的工作
on the work here.
帮我盯紧一点
Make sure nothing goes wrong,
千万别出什么差错
and prevent S2
让二部的人
from identifying any issues with us.
抓住咱们的把柄
I'll do my best to meet
夏总那边
Mr. Xia ASAP.
我会尽快安排见面
Don't worry.
放心吧
I'll get back to work now.
我先去忙了
[I'm going to the US to meet Mr. Xia.]
我打算飞去美国见夏总
[Tonight's flight.]
今天夜里的航班
[Where are you?]
你在哪儿呢
Ms. Geng!
耿小姐
Could you
麻烦您给我
spare a minute?
一分钟的时间
Please listen to me.
您听我说一下好吗
I beg you.
拜托您了
Just one minute.
就一分钟
Ms. Geng!
耿小姐
Please!
拜托了
Stop.
停车
Thank you!
谢谢您啊耿小姐
The offer
代瑞
Dairui gives to Weiji
能给惟纪公司的条件
will be the best.
一定是全星城最好的
With Professor Jia's backing,
加上贾教授的加持
I'm sure Mr. Xia wouldn't
我相信夏总
wanna miss it.
也不愿意错过这次机会
Ms. Tu,
涂小姐
threats won't work on me.
威胁对我没有用
Being persistent like this
你这样死缠烂打
is even less effective.
更没有用
You should go back.
快回去吧
I understand.
我知道
I just want to let you know
我就是想告诉您
that Ji Yuheng from Dairui
代瑞的纪昱恒
is actually my
其实是我
soon-to-be husband.
即将结婚的丈夫
Our relationship
我们俩个的关系
has always been hard to make public.
一直都不太好公开
I'm
我
not trying to
我这样做
threaten you.
不是要威胁您
I just want to help Yuheng.
就是想要帮帮他
Get in the car.
快上车吧
Thank you.
谢谢
What happened to you?
你什么造型啊这是
It's none of your business.
用不着你管
Are you trying to
你不会是
make a mess out of yourself
故意把自己搞成这样
to elicit sympathy from Yuheng?
让师哥心疼你吧
Move aside.
你让开
You're soaking wet!
淋成了这样
What if you catch a cold?
感冒了怎么办
I need to talk to you.
我有事跟你说
You don't need to go to the US anymore.
你不用去美国了
Mr. Xia is in China.
夏总他人在国内
I've met someone
我遇到了一个贵人
who has agreed to help arrange
她答应帮我们
a meeting tomorrow at 4:00 p.m.
明天下午四点约到夏总
Are you serious?
你开什么玩笑啊
- Tang Yuhui... - Tang Yuhui.
唐羽卉 唐羽卉
What's wrong with you?
你这个人怎么这样啊
For the result,
我有没有开玩笑
you'll see tomorrow, right?
明天不就知道了吗
Why do you
你怎么
always look down on others?
老是看不上别人呢
Fine.
行
I'll assume you've made it.
我就当你约上了
But I could have
但我一句话
settled this with one word.
就可以搞定的事
Look at you now,
看看你现在这样子
soaked like this.
淋成这样
You've gone through a lot, huh?
费了不少劲吧
If
你一句话
it's true,
就能搞定的事情
why didn't you do it sooner?
你为什么早不去做呢
You know my secret,
你不要以为自己
then are you trying
知道一点秘密
to threaten me?
就可以在这儿威胁人
I won't let you
我不会给你
use it against me!
把它变成武器的机会
Do you feel better now?
还难受吗
Much better.
不难受
Here,
来
try it and see if it's hot.
试试热不热啊
It's hot.
烫
As your supervisor,
作为领导啊
I appreciate your help.
还是要感谢你
But as your family,
不过作为爱人
I hope in the future,
我希望以后能不能
you won't make such rash decisions
别不跟我商量
without consulting me.
就做这种傻事啊
I'm really worried.
我会很担心的
As a subordinate,
作为下属
I think sales
营销本来
is inherently a tough job.
就是个辛苦的活吗
So I hope
那我希望
we can boost our performance.
加一点业绩
As your family,
作为爱人
I genuinely worry about you.
我担心你
I want to do everything I can
我想尽我所能地
to support you.
为你做点事
Besides,
再说了
who knows you've actually
谁知道你有
got a plan B.
备选方案啊
So it sounds like
那这么听起来
you don't have faith in me.
还是对我没信心啊
That's not true.
那可不是啊
Man,
真是的
I feel awful.
我好难受呀
I might be coming down with a cold.
我可能要感冒了
A bad one.
重感冒
And here I'm being
我的准老公还在这儿
lectured by my husband.
上纲上线地说我
Bah!
呸 呸 呸
Don't say that.
不能乱说话
Didn't we agree not to
咱俩不是说好了吗
discuss work at home?
在家不谈工作
No nagging, okay?
能不能别说我了
I need to tell you something
我想跟你说件
very serious.
很严肃的事
That Tang Yuhui,
那个唐羽卉
she knows
她知道
about our relationship.
我们两个的关系了
She has feelings for you.
她喜欢你呢
Everyone seems to know.
全世界的人都知道
Since she's aware of this,
她知道这件事
won't she be eager
会不会恨不得
to spill the beans?
马上就捅出去啊
So she could
好让我
have me pack my stuff and leave.
收拾收拾东西走人
How can you be so sure
你怎么就那么确定
that you'll leave?
最后一定是你走啊
We signed an earnout agreement.
咱们俩签了对赌协议呀
We have to stick to it.
肯定要按协议办事的
Although I'm not sure
虽然我不知道
what you progress is.
你的进度到哪儿了
However, I still haven't
但是我那五千万的
met my KPI
关键绩效指标
of fifty million.
还没有完成呀
If it gets exposed now,
如果现在捅出去了
I'll definitely be the one to go.
走的人肯定是我
Don't sweat it.
不用太过于担心
In the banking industry,
其实在银行里的呢
there are three types of people.
一般就三种人
Relying on
这第一种
their own skills,
是靠自己的本事
or on
第二种呢
family connections,
是靠家里的资源
or
第三种
on both.
是前两者都兼备的
Tang Yuhui
而唐羽卉
is exactly the third type.
恰恰就是这第三种
Such individuals
这种人呢
grow up in this environment.
他们从小就耳濡目染
They're good
习惯了
at assessing situations.
审时度势
They also tend to have
同时会有一点
a bit of arrogance.
小小的高傲
So whatever they choose to do
所以做任何事情
needs to be in their best interest.
都得是对他们有利的
Think about it.
仔细想想
Why didn't she expose us
唐羽卉如果在第一时间
in the first place?
没有曝光我们的话
She must feel
说明她一定觉得
that this situation
这件事情
is not beneficial to her at all.
对她没有任何好处
Well,
希望
I hope so.
按你说的这样吧
It's okay.
差不多了
Ginger soup can warm you up.
姜汤祛寒
So you should finish it up.
还是要一碗喝掉
[I can leave Dairui]
我可以为了和他在一起
[just to be with him.]
离开代瑞
[What about you?]
你敢吗
[If that day ever comes,]
如果真的有这么一天
[what choice will]
我和纪昱恒
[Ji Yuheng and I make?]
会做出怎样的选择呢
Just a moment, please.
麻烦两位稍等一下
Mingrui is still in a meeting.
明睿还在开会
His schedule is packed
他出国前这两天
these days before going abroad.
时间安排得特别满
We are supposed to be dating
今天这两个小时
for the next two hours.
本来是我们约会的时间
Thank you, Ms. Geng.
谢谢耿小姐
I really appreciate it.
真的非常感谢
[Hello, Mr. Xia.]
夏总
Who are they?
这两位是
This is Xiaoning,
这是筱柠
[a new friend I just met.]
是我刚认识的新朋友
[This is Mr. Ji,]
这位纪总
[her fiancé.]
是她的未婚夫
It's a pleasure.
幸会啊夏总
I'm Ji Yuheng
代瑞
from Dairui.
纪昱恒
Nice to meet you.
您好
You too.
你好
Tu Xiaoning, an account manager from Dairui.
代瑞客户经理涂筱柠
It's not easy
好不容易
to carve out time for a date.
挤出时间来约会
Why has it suddenly
怎么又突然
turned into work again?
变成工作了
Our date can wait.
约会又不急这一两次
Once the deal of your resort
等你度假村的事情
is settled,
落定了
you could spend quality time with me.
不就能好好陪我了
By the way,
对了
I heard that
我听说
there's a treasure in this city,
星城有座镇城之宝
the Nanshan Mountain.
南山
The temple in there is quite popular.
那里的寺庙香火挺旺的
I've always wanted to check it out,
我一直想去看看
but I haven't found a good guide yet.
但没有合适的导游
[Xiaoning,]
筱柠
[since you're a local,]
你是本地人
[would you be willing to show me around?]
你愿不愿意陪我去看看
My pleasure.
当然好了
We will leave you guys to it.
那你们慢慢聊
Let's go.
走
Have a seat.
坐
Mr. Ji,
纪总
I remember your proposal.
我记得你的方案
Having Professor Jia Ziqing
请贾子庆教授
serve as a financial advisor,
担任财务指导的建议
you really impressed me.
让我印象深刻呀
[This is]
这个呀
[a souvenir from our press conference.]
是我们发布会的纪念品
[It features the famous zodiac signs,]
著名的十二生肖
[for a kid's first birthday celebrations.]
也是给孩子抓周用的
[I'll take this one.]
我现在付钱吧
[OK.]
好嘞
Ms. Geng,
耿小姐
thank you so much!
谢谢你啊
No problem.
没事
This is the first time I've met your fiancé.
今天见到了你的未婚夫
He's indeed outstanding.
果然很耀眼
You're
你们
secretly married because of work,
是因为工作的关系
right?
才隐婚的
Yeah.
对
You even had to fight for
你连帮他争取
the chance to see Mingrui,
见到明睿的机会
and that's why
都是迫不得已
you revealed your relationship.
才透露你们的关系
I completely
这种感觉
understand where you're coming from.
我非常能理解
Love is the hardest thing to conceal.
相爱是最难以掩饰的
Yet,
偏偏
happiness cannot be shared,
快乐不能与人分享
and pain cannot be expressed.
痛苦不能与人诉说
So I'm willing to lend a hand.
所以我愿意成全你们
Also a way to gather blessings for myself.
也算是为我自己积福吧
Thank you for your understanding.
谢谢你的成全
I also believe that what you seek
我也相信你所求的
will surely be answered.
一定能得到回应
Let's go.
走吧
When it comes to a large company
所以面对惟纪
like Weiji,
这样的大公司
I believe
我相信
that all banks
无论是哪家银行
are willing to provide
都会在贷款的期限
the best solutions
额度
in terms of loan terms, amount,
以及利率上
and interest rates.
给到最优解
As for Xingcheng,
那星城
as a pilot for Weiji Resort
作为惟纪度假村
to expand into second-tier cities,
向二线城市发展的试点
it has different consumer demands
它也有着不同于
compared to first-tier cities.
一线城市的消费需求
Therefore, financial service plans
所以金融服务方案
also need to align with
也需要符合
local market demands
当地的市场需求
and customer structure.
和客户结构
This makes it difficult to simply
这就很难照搬
replicate and duplicate past experiences.
和复刻以往的经验
But you can rest assured.
不过您可以放心
We at Dairui
我们代瑞
will fully cooperate with Professor Jia
会全力配合贾教授
to start from
从惟纪的
your economic needs
现实经济需求出发
to optimize financing solutions
优化符合
that align with the economic
二线城市经济特性
characteristics of second-tier cities.
且易于推广的融资方案
You've made yourself
你刚才说的
crystal clear.
我都听明白了
I'll have my assistant
后续我会交代助理
reach out to you for the details.
跟你做具体的对接
So,
那
are you saying...
夏总您的意思是
The structure and details
你刚才说的
you're saying
方案结构和细节
are much clearer than those in the files.
比资料文件里直观得多
Let's work towards a strategic alignment.
我们走战略合作协议吧
Alright,
那
sounds good.
行
So,
那这样
on behalf of Dairui,
我代表我们代瑞
I want to express my gratitude
感谢您的支持
for your support and trust.
和信任
As rumored,
看来
you're quite aware
夏总跟传闻中一样
of
很知道
the importance of time,
时间的重要性
not wasting too much on comparisons.
不浪费比较和纠结上
Excessive comparison is pointless.
太多的比较没有意义
What I choose
我选定的
will undoubtedly be the best option.
一定是最好的
Let's head out now.
现在走
Before the
离下个会
next meeting,
开会之前
we can still meet up with our wives.
还能接着老婆
Would you like to tag along?
要一起吗
Absolutely.
好啊
Let's go.
走
You have played a crucial role
这次能拿下
in securing
惟纪这个项目
the Weiji project.
你是功不可没呀
Tell me,
说
as soon as the news was out,
是不是消息刚散出去
many already came to recruit you, right?
就有不少人来挖你了
Sir, a supervisor
老师
from the headquarters came for a meeting
总行领导过来开会
and suddenly requested to see me.
突然说要见我
Is it also because of the deal with Weiji?
也是因为惟纪的事吗
Yes, it is.
是啊
Please come in.
来 请进
Hello, President Xu.
许行长
Mr. Zhou.
周总
It's been a while.
好久不见 好久不见
Indeed.
是啊
Let me introduce.
我给您介绍一下
This is
这位就是
Ji Yuheng, the manager of S1.
拿下惟纪的大功臣
He's the key player in securing
拓展一部的部门经理
the Weiji case.
纪昱恒
A pleasure, sir.
领导您好
Young and talented!
年轻有为呀
Your future is promising.
未来可期
Thank you.
您过奖了
If it weren't for
要不是因为
my team's collective efforts,
手下的兵冲在前面
I might not have
我也不一定
secured this opportunity.
能拿下这个良机
I've also
这个事呢
heard about it.
我也听说了
What's the name of that rookie?
那个新人叫什么了
Her name is Tu...
叫 涂
Tu Xiaoning.
涂筱柠
Mr Li,
李叔
here's the receipt for this transaction.
这是这次的存款回单
I came for business nearby.
我刚好在附近办事
I heard you're here,
听说您在这儿
so I brought it over for you.
就给您送过来了
Thank you.
辛苦卉卉啦
What would you like to drink?
你想喝点什么
Tell me.
李叔帮你点
No, thank you.
不用了
It's working hours.
我这现在在工作呢
Not a good time.
不太方便
Let's save it for next time.
等下次吧
On my day off,
等休息日
I'll visit you
我跟我爸
with my dad.
一块过去拜访您
That sounds good.
也行 也行
Your team
你们部门
secured the Weiji project,
拿下惟纪的事啊
and in less than half an afternoon,
不到半个下午的时间
the news spread throughout the industry.
就传遍了整个业界
You've really made a splash this time.
这次可风光大了
Just be honest with me,
你给李叔透个底
was it your dad
是你爸
that hooked it up for you?
给你搭的线吧
No, not my dad.
不是我爸
Mr. Ji from our team
是我们部门的纪总
found the contact information
他通过自己的渠道
through his own connections.
找到了对方的联系方式
Ji Yuheng.
纪昱恒
Your senior from college, right?
你那个师哥对吧
Your university
你们大学
really produces outstanding talent!
真是人才辈出啊
About what I mentioned last time,
上次李叔跟你提的那事
you should give it some thought.
你再考虑考虑呗
You know, I've been
你说我跟你爸
close with your dad for years.
称兄道弟这些年
Just come to Shunjue and work for me.
你到舜决当财务经理
I will offer you the best package.
李叔亏待不了你
Salary, benefits,
薪资 福利
you name it.
随便提
Um,
李叔
how about
这样吧
giving me more time?
您再给我点时间
I'll think it over.
我考虑考虑
You said it, alright?
你说的啊
You can't give me
不能再跟上次一样
the runaround again.
敷衍我
Rest assured,
放心吧
this time I will
这次我肯定
definitely give it serious thought.
会认真考虑的
Good, good.
好 好 好
Get up, it's time for work.
起来上班了
Was this one taken in Xihai Town?
这个照片西海镇拍的
Isn't it beautiful?
美吗
Who gave you permission to put this here?
谁允许你放这儿了
There are portrait rights involved.
有肖像权的
I can display my own girlfriend,
我摆我自己的女朋友
can't I?
还不行啊
What?
谁是你女朋友
When did I agree
我什么时候答应
to be your girlfriend?
做你女朋友了
No backing out from this.
不许反悔
What are you laughing about?
笑什么
No backing out, no backing out!
不许反悔 不许反悔
Once you move in,
等你正式搬过来
I'll convert this desk
我就把这张桌子
into a dresser
给你改成
for you.
化妆台
Then you can do
然后你每天早上都可以
your makeup here
在这里
every morning.
涂脂抹粉
What about you?
你干吗
You'll be
你在
by my side,
旁边
having some
对我
dirty thoughts about me?
想入非非啊
Am I not allowed?
不可以啊
How far is your home from the company?
你家离公司多远
Forty minutes drive.
四十分钟
We've got half an hour until clock-in.
还有半个小时就打卡了
What's that phone of yours for?
你那个手机是干吗的
Just for show?
摆设吗
It doesn't even have an alarm!
连个闹钟都没有
Who unplugged my charging cable
是谁把我的手机充电线
last night and
昨天晚上拔了
plugged in their own?
插自己的手机上了
Now my phone is dead.
那我手机连个电都没有
Am I supposed to rely on willpower to get up?
还能靠意志力响不成
It's going to be a vibrant day!
元气满满的一天
Good morning, Jing!
静姐早
Morning, Jing.
早啊 静姐
Good morning.
早
Good morning, Fanggang.
小赵哥早
What?
干吗呢
Sneaking around
大早上的
early in the morning,
鬼鬼祟祟地
that was spooky!
吓死人
Fanggang,
小赵哥
you're late.
迟到啦
Are you giving up on your precious?
命根子不要啦
I mean, attendance bonus.
全勤奖
I had
我这个
some issues at home this morning,
今儿早上家里边有点事
which caused the delay.
耽搁了
You've been acting strange lately.
小赵哥你最近不太对啊
Last week, you refused to work overtime
上个星期加班三倍工资
for three times your salary
你都不加班
because of family matters.
说家里有事
That's not like you.
不太正常
You guys...
你们这帮人啊
When I was ambitious before,
那我之前上进的时候
I worked overtime every day.
天天加班
When you invited me out for drinks,
你们约我出去喝酒
I didn't go, and you said I didn't care.
我不去你们说我不在乎
So now I'm
那我现在
indifferent to fame and fortune,
淡泊名利了
leaving opportunities to you all.
把机会都留给你们
Here you go again, questioning me.
又来质疑我
You may be indifferent to those,
名利是淡泊了
but in other aspects,
但是其他方面一定是
you must get more intense, right?
浓烈起来了吧
[Family issues?]
家事
They must
赵哥
not be trivial.
你这个家事不是小事啊
[It's a big deal.]
是大事
Are you dating?
谈对象了
I guessed it right, huh?
你谈对象啦
He has a girlfriend now!
他有对象了
C'mon.
小赵哥
You're being too distant!
你太不仗义了吧
Such a big news,
这么大事
and you didn't even share with us.
你都不跟大家伙说一说
When will you bring her
什么时候把嫂子
to meet us?
带出来见一见
I...
我 我
I've been busy
我这两天这个
with the Weiji contract
跟惟纪公司签合同
these days.
比较忙嘛
How about
这样吧
I treat you all
过一阵
to a meal sometime later?
我请大家吃饭
Are you serious?
同行吗
Look!
你看这新闻
Our
咱们
partnership with Weiji
看来是跟惟纪公司
seems to be finalized.
合作聊妥了
That watch
这夏总
Mr. Xia is wearing
戴的表
is pretty expensive.
挺贵啊
When did you start analyzing watches?
你怎么研究上表了
Did you get a new one?
你换表啦
Nice!
你这可以呀
Look at our boss.
你看咱领导
[He's been wearing]
那老款的表
[the same old model for ages.]
戴了多长时间了
[Low-key!]
多低调啊
[Yeah.]
是
Is everyone here?
都在呢
I've got
有个消息
an announcement to make.
跟大家宣布一下
Um, Yuhui is meeting a client.
那个小唐去见客户了
Pass it on to her later.
回头你转告一下
Sure.
好
The contract with Weiji
惟纪公司的合约
has been officially secured.
我们正式落定了
Thanks for
也辛苦大家
all your hard work,
这段时间的努力
especially you, Xiaoning.
尤其是要感谢一下小涂
[Well, Jing,]
行静姐
your trainee seems
您这个徒弟啊
to surpass you.
是彻底出师了
I mean, braver than you.
胆子比您还大
I'm happy to see it.
我乐见其成
One more.
还有一个消息啊
I'm excited to say
要跟大家宣布一下
that Mr. Xia invited us
夏总正式邀请我们下周
[to tour one of]
去惟纪已经
[his operating resort projects]
营运的度假村项目
[next week.]
去做考察
It's been a while
咱部门已经
since our dept had an outing.
很久没有过团建了
We're allowed for
这次行里特批我们
paid leave for this trip.
带薪休假
Time to relax!
好好放松一下吧
Fantastic!
太好了
A trip, finally!
可以出去玩啦
Time for drinks!
可以喝酒了
All right, back to work.
回去工作吧
Move it.
去 去 去
About that friend of his...
他那个闺蜜
Enough, enough.
行了 行了 行了
Ms. Rao,
饶经理
I have a client
我这边有个客户啊
who keeps mentioning
他一直说
something about your side...
就是觉得你这边
Come here.
来我给你看一下
When did you buy this?
什么时候买的
Before I came up.
上来前买的
How is it,
怎么样
any issues?
他们有问题吗
Nope.
没问题
Great.
好
Have a taste.
记得吃啊
Get lost.
快滚 快滚吧
[Got time after work?]
下班有空吗
[Let's go shopping.]
陪我购物去呗
Are you seriously buying a watch?
真的要买手表
You used to stash
你一个之前连一块钱
every penny in high-yield
都要放在什么代瑞
savings account,
钱钱宝里拿利息的
but suddenly is splurging?
现在这么舍得下血本了
I wonder
我看那个纪昱恒
what kind of luck Ji Yuheng had
上辈子不知道到底是
in his past life.
修了什么洪福大德
Keep it low-key.
低调 低调
Facing so many social engagements,
他应酬多
he should have a decent watch.
应该有块像样的手表
I've managed our money so long,
我管钱管了这么久
but never thought
我都没想过
about getting him a gift.
要给他买一个礼物
Now that
正好
he's sealed the deal with Weiji,
他这次搞定了惟纪
it's a perfect excuse to celebrate.
就当是给他庆祝了
A luxury watch?
拿下惟纪就送名表
Aren't you being extravagant?
至于这么豪横吗
It's worth it!
当然至于了
Securing Weiji
他拿下的可是惟纪
means
这样
he's more likely
他就更有可能
to move up to the Ji'an branch.
去集安分行了
This watch
我给他买一块表
is my way
就当作
of preemptively celebrating.
给他提前庆祝一下
Besides,
而且过两天
my birthday's coming up.
我不是过生日吗
He's definitely getting me something,
他一定给我买礼物
then
到时候
I can whip out this watch
我就马上拿出
as a return gift.
这块表当回礼
He'll be over the moon.
你说他是不是感动坏了
The key is
就主打一个
to keep him under control.
狠狠地拿捏住他
Alright.
行 行 行
You're more liberal than I'm now.
你现在可比我豪横多了
I've been under constant attack
我现在被刺客
by all these hidden expenses.
频频刺伤啊
Assassins rise from
你知不知道
everywhere, you know,
超市刺客就算了
supermarkets, ice cream,
竟然还有什么雪糕刺客
duck neck,
鸭脖刺客
even power bank!
连充电宝都是刺客
Ever since I had that
自打我上次跟齐郁
money argument with Qi Yu,
因为钱的事闹矛盾以来
I've been trying
我就想着
to survive on my
看能不能拿自己的工资
salary alone.
养活自己
But
结果
my 3,000 yuan paycheck
我那三千块钱的工资
vanishes
在现实面前
like sand
就像海滩上的一撮沙
on a beach.
一吹就没了
The power of love
我觉得爱情的力量
is truly amazing.
真的好伟大
It can even change your views on money.
竟然能改变你的金钱观
How about giving the high-yield
代瑞钱钱宝
savings account another thought?
要不你考虑一下吧
Stop teasing me.
你别贫我了
I'm not even
我现在
using my dad's card anymore.
都不刷我爸的卡了
surviving on
自己的工资
my salary is a struggle,
连活下去都是问题
let alone saving anything.
更别说能存钱了
When you're back on your feet,
没事等你有钱了
I'll help you with some investments.
我好好给你找个理财
Hope that day
希望那天
comes soon.
尽快来临吧
What are you looking at?
你看什么呢
Nothing, nothing.
没什么 没什么
Don't be mad.
别生气了吗
You go get a divorce or I'll go!
我再也不信你会离婚了
They look really familiar.
那两个人好眼熟啊
That guy is...
那个男的是
Oh, no!
你别指
I'll buy you
一会儿
a bag later.
买一个包
The latest model,
最新款
OK?
好吗
Shopping and stumbling upon
逛街还能吃到
such a juicy bit of gossip,
这么大一个瓜
unbelievable.
不得了 不得了
You can indulge in any gossip.
谁的瓜你都敢吃
Stop looking.
别看了
Don't look.
你不许看啊
After we buy the watch,
等会买完手表
I'll treat you to something good.
我请你吃好吃的
Really?
真的假的
I'm gonna order something expensive.
那我可得吃顿贵的
You know,
你是不知道
I've been downgraded
我最近呢
in everything lately,
为了实施什么
just to stick to the principle of
赚多少花多少的原则
spending within the earned money.
吃个饭都消费降级了
I'll upgrade it for you later.
我一会儿给你升回来
Come on.
走
This is your first birthday
咱们在一起以后
after we get married.
你的第一个生日
We can't celebrate it alone.
就没法单独给你过了
But a gift is still a must.
但是礼物可不能少
What have you prepared for me?
你给我准备什么礼物了
It's a secret.
秘密
A secret, huh?
还秘密
Do you think
你说
our colleagues
咱们同事
know it's my birthday?
知道我过生日吗
Maybe
会不会
they're planning a surprise?
给我准备一个惊喜啊
How would I know?
这我哪儿能知道呀
You, Zhao Fanggang, and Rao Jing
你赵方刚和饶静
are always plotting something
天天在你们那小群里面
in the group of yours.
谋划一些什么
Will you tell me,
难道会告诉
your boss?
我这个领导吗
How do you know
你怎么知道
we have a group chat?
我们有小群啊
So, there is one.
看来还真有啊
I guessed it right.
被我给猜到了
You're so cunning.
老谋深算
If I was sold by you,
你这个人真的是啊
I would still help you
有一天我被你卖了
count the money!
还得帮你数钱呢
No way,
不行
I want a refund.
我要退货
Too late for that now.
现在可退不了了
Where is my conditioner?
我护发素好像没带
No worries,
没事
I'll grab it for you.
我给你取
Wait a second.
等我一下啊
♪I make the birds♪
我让小鸟欣然
♪sing praises around me.♪
围着赞叹
♪I make the flowers♪
我让花朵嫣然
♪bloom and sway.♪
围着摇颤
♪I make the fish♪
我让鱼儿跃然
♪leap and chase.♪
围着追赶
♪The beauty is overwhelming,♪
秀色饱餐
♪everything adores it.♪
当然万物喜欢
♪I make♪
我让矜持怦然
♪the aloof hearts flutter.♪
撩起波澜
♪the indifferent dream.♪
撩起梦幻
[Why aren't you]
大家这么热闹
[joining in on the fun?]
你怎么不跟着一起啊
♪Oh my God.♪
哎呀 妈呀
♪What do I do?♪
天呐 怎么办
[Do you want to hear me sing?]
想听我唱
[Of course,]
当然
[I haven't]
我好久没听
[heard you sing for long.]
我们纪先生唱歌了
♪I'm just so good-looking!♪
我怎么这么好看
Alright, stop it!
行了 行了 行了
This song
这歌吧
isn't a must anyway.
它也不是非唱不可啊
[How good it should have been!]
这原来挺好的一首歌
But you butchered it beyond recognition!
被你们唱得稀碎
Honestly, you're making me feel...
听得我真的就是有点
nauseous.
这犯恶心我都
Are you really feeling unwell?
姐 你真不舒服啊
Maybe I've been
可能前一段时间
under too much work pressure lately.
工作压力实在是太大了
[Now that Mr. Ji]
你说纪总
[suddenly]
突然给咱们放假
[gave us a break,]
这一下放松下来了
I feel a bit off after relaxing.
觉着有点不太舒服
Well, Fanggang, stop here.
那就别唱了小赵哥
Forget it.
不唱了 不唱了
[Are you okay?]
你没事吧
[Did I really make you feel this way?]
真是被我唱成这样的
Feeling better?
不难受了
Jing, are you in love?
姐你谈恋爱了吧
Tell me the truth!
是不是谈恋爱了
You're smiling
你怎么笑的
like a lovestruck girl!
跟少女怀春一样
What?
不是
Isn't it normal
姐总谈恋爱
for me to be in love?
这不很正常吗
Why are you
不是谈个恋爱
making such a fuss?
像全村的希望似的
Look at your eyes!
你看你们那眼神
But now,
这次看起来
you seem to get true love.
像是遇到了真爱
I get the same vibe.
我觉得也不太一样
Is it
这次谈的是
a charming young guy
阳光小弟弟啊
or a reserved, cool one?
还是禁欲小哥哥呀
Well...
就
neither
不是小弟弟
is correct.
也不是小哥哥
He's an old guy.
是个老哥哥
He must be really handsome.
肯定长得很帅吧
Or, you wouldn't be interested.
要不然你肯定看不上
Xiaoning,
筱柠那姐
I have to tell you,
不得不跟你说一下
he's more handsome
就这长相啊
than Daniel Wu,
赛吴彦祖
more brooding
这忧郁的气质呢
than Tony Leung,
赛梁朝伟
and more skilled
身手
than Donnie Yen.
赛甄子丹
Really? No way!
真的呀 我的妈
And when it comes to singing,
就你们刚唱那歌
he's like Jacky Cheung.
他唱歌赛张学友
[No way!]
我去
That's amazing!
太棒了
[Rao Jing,]
饶静
[you have a back-up, right?]
你是不是有二心
[Does this description]
你描述这个人
[even match me?]
跟我搭边吗
Alright,
行了不跟你们
enough joking around.
开玩笑了啊
Listen.
刚姐都逗你们的
His best trait
这个人
is that
最大的一个优点呢
he's
就是他
very self-aware.
特别的有自知之明
♪Secretly,♪
偷偷 偷偷
♪you stole my heart.♪
偷走我的心
OK,
好
thanks.
谢谢啊
You go ahead.
你先办
Here you are.
来
I know you've been
知道大家最近这段时间
working really hard lately,
工作得都很辛苦
juggling both performance goals
又得完成绩效
and handling clients.
又得忙着应付客户
So for this team-building trip,
那这次咱们团建
no matter how much
不管行里
the bank reimburses,
给报销多少费用
I'll cover all the
其他产生的一切费用
additional costs.
我来买单
Our goal here
我们主打的就是一个
is to have fun!
开心 快乐
Mr. Ji is right.
纪总说得对
We're here
出来玩大家图的
to have a good time, after all.
就是一个开心
Absolutely.
对
Mr. Ji,
纪总
how about
今晚
a whole roasted lamb tonight?
整只烤全羊吃
Sure,
行
no problem.
没问题
This year, our branch
今年咱们星城分行
has outshined the competition,
傲视群雄都这么痛快
so if we top sales next year,
那明年要是咱拿个销冠
how about a trip to Antarctica?
是不是得去南极团建呀
[That's too cold.]
那地儿太冷了
[Just go, if you want.]
要去你自己去吧
[I'd rather go to Africa]
我宁可去非洲
[to witness the great]
我去看动物
animal migration.
大迁徙
Typical taste.
你那品位
Attention,
来 来 来
the rooms are all set.
房间都已经开好了
Yuhui,
小唐
you'll share
你和
with Miss Yao.
大小姚一间
Sorry,
我不行
but I can't do that.
我睡觉特别浅
I'm a light sleeper.
我不能跟别人睡一间
Fine.
行
[I'll get you]
那一会儿
[a single room.]
我再给你开一个单间
[Keep your ID handy.]
你把你的身份证拿好
[Alright,]
好
[thanks.]
谢谢
[We three will share a room.]
我们仨老爷们一间啊
[Okay.]
好嘞
I'll return your ID later.
身份证回头给你们
Okay.
行
Rao Jing,
饶静
you'll share with Xiaoning.
你跟小涂住一间
Here.
来
[Fanggang,]
赵哥
who's sharing
那个纪总
with Mr. Ji?
跟谁一间啊
He has a room to himself,
纪总单独住一间
separate from us.
跟我们不在一个区
Got it.
行
Let's all
那咱们
go freshen up
都先回去收拾收拾
and meet at the pool later.
一会儿泳池见
Sounds good.
好嘞
Let's go.
走吧
The view here
这景色看着
is pretty nice.
是挺不错的啊
And fresh air.
空气很清新
Nice!
好
Ms. Rao.
饶经理
Good swim!
游得好
Come down!
下来游两圈啊
Sh!
游你的吧
Keep quiet.
少说两句话
Happy holiday.
假期愉快
I've got something to say.
我突然想起个事
What's the topic?
聊什么呢
Listen to him.
他说呢
A few days ago,
前两天我同事
a colleague called me
给我打电话
and asked
问我
if depression
你们这行
common in our line of work.
抑郁症多不多呀
I thought about it later.
我后来一想
I don't know about
咱银行其他部门
other depts,
我不知道
but for client managers...
但咱们这客户经理
When we're busy,
一忙起来
who has time to get depressed?
哪有时间得这病啊
Exactly.
是
Those who
而且现在
owe money are the real bosses.
欠钱的人是大爷
The other day,
前几天我好言好语
I made dozens of polite calls.
打了几十通电话
A boss just said,
结果老板心情不好
"Isn't it
跟我说
a bit of interest
不就是
I owe? What are you
欠你们几个利息吗
in a hurry for?"
催什么催呀
You don't say.
可不是吗
Then he hung up
然后挂了电话
and still didn't pay.
还是不给钱
[Yeah,]
对
[they wait until the central bank]
非得等到人民银行
[shuts down the system,]
把系统都关了
then transfer a hundred thousand
然后再把整百万的利息
in 5,0000 yuan increments,
五万五万的转进来
making it a hassle for everyone.
搞得人是劳神又费力
They take this work seriously.
几个人挺认真
Talking about work on a holiday.
出来还聊工作
And when they
而且等他们
need money,
要用钱的时候吧
they call you like crazy,
拼了命给你打电话
not letting you sleep,
不让你睡觉
keeping an eye on you 24/7
二十四小时
until you release the funds.
盯着你让你放款
That
你一说到这个
reminds me.
我想起来了
Once,
有一次
a female accountant
一个女财务
[pulled up a chair right behind me,]
拉个椅子坐我身后
[staring at me]
跟个监视器一样
[like a security camera.]
就这么死盯着我
[I couldn't take it anymore,]
我后来实在忍不住了
[so I went to the restroom.]
我上个厕所吧
[Guess what she said?]
你猜人怎么说
["The loan hasn't been approved yet.]
我们这贷款没下来呢
Where do you think you're going?"
瞎跑什么呀
Yeah,
对 对 对
it's so annoying.
烦死了
Unbearable.
没法干这工作
I'm going for another swim.
我再去游两圈
Okay.
好
Let's go.
走
Wait, my shoes...
等会儿我把鞋
Test the water.
试试水
[How's the water?]
咋样
Mr. Zhao,
赵经理
when did you get cupping done?
什么时候拔的罐
Feeling a bit under the weather lately?
最近身子有点虚呀
This rubber duck is cute.
这小黄鸭挺可爱啊
Yeah.
是啊
Luckily, I dodged my period this time,
幸亏躲过了例假期
or else
要不然这次
it would've ruined the trip.
出来玩都玩不好
Yeah,
对啊
getting your period on a trip is the worst.
例假期出来玩最麻烦了
What did you just say?
你刚说什么
I said I was lucky
我说我躲过例假期
to avoid my period.
挺幸运的
Look,
静姐你看
a duck.
鸭子
Rao Jing!
饶静
Dear friends,
家人们朋友们
today,
今天呢
we gather here
咱们欢聚在这里啊
not just for the team-building
不仅仅是为了
or the roast lamb.
咱们团建吃这只烤羊子
More importantly,
更重要的一件事情
we should celebrate
这是咱们
the birthday of one
一位小伙伴的生日
of our colleagues.
要去庆祝
28 years ago,
二十八年前呢
she came into this world.
她呱呱坠地
And now,
二十八年后
she has become
她已经成为了
an outstanding member
我们拓展一部的
of our S1.
优秀标兵
Congrats!
她就是
Tu Xiaoning!
涂筱柠
Thank you.
谢谢
[Come up]
来
[and say something.]
上来说两句吧
Thank you, Fanggang.
谢谢小赵哥
[Thank you, everyone.]
谢谢大家
[Honestly, I had a feeling]
其实我刚刚有想过
[that you'll celebrate my birthday.]
你们会给我过生日
[But when it got close to midnight]
但是都快到十二点了
and no one mentioned it,
我看你们都没有反应
I thought you had forgotten.
我以为你们给忘了呢
I'm really happy to have you
很开心跟大家
by my side at work.
可以成为同事
I'd like to
我要
express my gratitude to you in turn.
一一感谢一下
Since I joined the S1,
我自从来到一部呢
I've received
接受到了
so much help from everyone.
大家太多的帮助
When I was feeling down,
在我最失意的时候
Jing
是静姐
always encouraged me.
总是鼓励我
Fanggang has tried best
我业绩不好的时候呢
to help me improve my performance.
是小赵哥手把手地教我
And
还有
two Miss Yao,
大姚 小姚
Xu Li,
许力哥
and Li Xiang
李想哥
were always
遇到任何麻烦
the first to help me
你们总是会
whenever I faced trouble.
第一时间来帮我
I'm grateful to all of you.
特别感谢你们
I also wanna thank my old colleague,
还有我的老同事
Yuhui.
小唐
Her presence
她的到来呢
reminds me to work harder
让我知道我更应该努力
and keep going.
努力进步
Lastly, thanks a million,
我还想感谢
Mr. Ji.
纪总
He has always encouraged
他一直鼓励我
and trusted me,
也非常地信任我
helping me grow
让我从一个
from someone knowing
什么都不懂的
nothing about sales
销售小白
into someone
成为了现在这样
who can now
算是可以
handle things on her own.
独当一面的人吧
I really enjoy this feeling
我很喜欢这种
of fighting alongside you all.
可以并肩作战的感觉
Thank you
谢谢你
all.
们
I much appreciate it.
谢谢你们
Cool!
好
Let's say
让我们一起
happy birthday
祝小涂
to
生日
Xiaoning!
快乐
Happy birthday!
生日快乐
Thanks.
谢谢
Let me add some more for you,
再给你加点
Ms. Rao.
饶经理
No, thanks.
不用了谢谢
Been waiting so long.
等半天了
[Can't wait to dig in.]
馋死了
[I don't eat this.]
不吃这个
[Go ahead.]
你吃 你吃 你吃
Excuse me.
各位
Today is Xiaoning's birthday.
今天呢是筱柠的生日
I wanna take this chance
我想借这个机会
to announce something.
跟大家说一件事情
[Is she about]
她不会要在这儿
[to reveal]
曝光我
[my relationship with Ji Yuheng?]
和纪昱恒的关系吧
I'm going to say it out
那这件事情呢
through a song.
我就用一首歌来表示吧
A song?
唱歌呀
Good!
好
[She's talented, huh?]
挺有才的啊
[She can sing.]
还会唱歌呢
[I didn't expect this.]
我真没想到呢还
Something's up.
有情况
♪You're the most important to me.♪
我想你是我最重要的人
♪Every little thing about you♪
所有关于你的点滴
♪matters more than I imagined.♪
比想象中还在意
♪You're the most important to me.♪
我想你是我最重要的人
♪My wish is in these short seasons,♪
最大心愿是有限季节
♪to spend more time♪
多点时间
♪with you.♪
在你身边
Maybe I should get up there
要不一会儿上去
and sing one for you too?
我也给你唱一个
Get lost.
滚
♪You're the most important to me.♪
我最重要的人
A birthday party into a confession.
生日局变表白局
This is too juicy.
真刺激
♪Every little thing about you♪
所有关于你的点滴
♪matters more than I imagined.♪
比想象中还在意
♪You're the most important to me.♪
我想你是我最重要的人
♪My wish is in these short seasons,♪
最大心愿是有限季节
♪to spend more time♪
多点时间
♪with you.♪
在你身边
Attention!
来
Watch your step and get board
大家注意脚下安全
in an orderly manner.
有序上车
Guys.
来
Listen!
同学们安静一下
The bus can't
一班人多
accommodate the entire Class 1.
他们车里坐不下
Please share some seats
你们挪几个位置
with them.
给他们坐
Okay.
好
Hurry up!
你不坐我坐